Aerie Blomberg

(706)436-3318

aerieblomberg@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Customer service professional with 4+ years of experience striving to exceed customer expectations and deliver high quality results. Future Civil Engineer sparked by curiosities in conception, design, construction, and maintenance of infrastructure projects and systems in both the public and private sector. Driven to provide infrastructure solutions while protecting and restoring the environment through innovation and imagination. Well versed and fluent in technology with a desire to educate businesses in automation, create efficiencies, and improve productivity.

EXPERIENCE

DAIRY QUEEN

Hartwell, GA

Quick Service restaurant Customer Service Agent

June 2018-January 2023

- Maintained high standards of customer service during high-volume, fast-paced operations.
- Built loyal clientele through friendly interactions with customers by expressing consistent appreciation.
- Resolved customer complaints promptly and professionally.
- Designated trainer on site for new employees.
- Communicated respectfully and positively with coworkers and management.
- Versatile to work all positions in the restaurant.

TARGET

Atlanta, GA

Fullfillment specialist

June 2018-January 2023

- Maintained times exceedingly well during the busiest of times.
- Learned the workflow and best practices in a time-frame exceeding expectations.
- Trained new employees after two months of employment.
- Communicated respectfully and positively with coworkers and management.

EDUCATION

KENNESAW STATE UNIVERSITY

Marietta, GA August 2020 to Present

Major: Civil Engineering, Minor: Computer Science Affiliations

- Member of the Civil Engineering Hours Society
- President of ITE Chapter
- Founder/Treasurer of the Board Game Club

Awards

Dean's List x2

HART COUNTY HIGH SCHOOL

Hartwell, GA August 2017 to May 2021

High School Diploma Projects

Projects

- Video game design with TSA
- Vex Robotics
- Leadership Hart

Awards

- Honor roll x5
- National Champions Video Game Design TSA
- State Champions Video Game Design TSA x2
- State Champions Robotics SkillsUSA

SKILLS

- Excellent Customer Service
- Fluent in Technology
- Certified in Microsoft Office
- Years of experience with numerous computer issues
- Experience as a web Developer
- Problem Solving
- Team oriented
- Great Mentor

REFERENCES

Mark Seabolt, Owner Hartwell Dairy Queen - (706)318-0395; seaboltproperties@gmail.com

Joy Yergan, Manager Hartwell Dairy Queen - (706)308-8595

Parth Bhavsar, Teacher Kennesaw State University - pbhavsar@kennesaw.edu